A Guide to the Withers Family Papers, 1855-1954, Undated
Special Collections, Kegley Library, Wytheville Community College
- Correspondence 1855-1954, Undated, 158 folders
  - Folder 121. Correspondence - Betty Ellison Withers Putney - Miscellaneous 1881 - 29 October 1905, 9 items. (Series-folder 1:121)
    Correspondents include: Susan Dabney Williams, Janet Ann Withers Cook, Elizabeth Hamlett Williams, L. Coolidge, Robert Enoch Withers, William Page Dame, and Elizabeth Elb.
  - Folder 122. Correspondence - Betty Ellison Withers Putney - Miscellaneous 23 November 1905 - 27 November 1905, 20 items. (Series-folder 1:122)
    Correspondents include: Janet Anne Withers Cook Boyd, Phoebe Holt, Elizabeth E. Coolidge, W. m> Dame, Eliza G. Massey, Virginia Secessia Withers Terry, Elizabeth Royall Withers Carter, Elizabeth Hamlett Williams Paxton, Carrie Royall Thomas, Lucy Maupin, Josephine Withers Read, Sally D. Royall, Anna Clay Crenshaw, Sue M. Graham, Mrs. E. M. Langhorne, and Major and Mrs. Sanders.
  - Folder 123. Correspondence - Betty Ellison Withers Putney - Miscellaneous November 1905 - 1907, 13 items. (Series-folder 1:123)
    Correspondents include: Alma M. Cowardin, Ashley C. Dempsey, Ethel Gaines, Kathrynne Holt, Elizabeth Henry Lyons, N. V. Tudor, John H. Fowle, Mary Thornhill Williams, and Janet Ann Withers Cook Boyd.
  - Folder 124. Correspondence - Betty Ellison Withers Putney - Miscellaneous Undated, 5 items. (Series-folder 1:124)
    Correspondents include: A. L. Elliott Jr. and Willie Clare Withers.
  - Folder 125. Correspondence - Willie Clare Withers 1881-1893, 17 items. (Series-folder 1:125)
    Correspondents include: Josephine Withers Read, Geoff H. Zimmerman, Rosa Bemis, H. L. Taylor, George W. Arthur, J. G. Duncan, Withers Massie, Alilce Withers Goggins, and George H. Zimmerman.
  - Folder 126. Correspondence - Willie Clare Withers 1894-1909, Undated, 14 items. (Series-folder 1:126)
    Correspondents include: George H. Zimmerman, a physician who practiced in the coal boom town of Pocahontas, Virginia; P. P. Carter, Lizzie R. Poage, May Walton Kent, M. I. Wilson, C. G. Alley, Maggie Whistle, Mrs. Hunt, and Tyler Claiborne.
  - Folder 127. Correspondence - William Patton Kent to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1906-1909, 6 items; photocopies. (Series-folder 1:127)
    Regarding life as consul in Guatemala City, Guatemala.
  - Folder 128. Correspondence - William Patton Kent to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1919-1931, 10 items. (Series-folder 1:128)
    Re: social and diplomatic life in Washington, D. C.; William Nuckles Doak; Tyler Gatewood Kent.
  - Folder 129. Correspondence - William Patton Kent 1932-1935, 12 items. (Series-folder 1:129)
    Re: Tyler Gatewood Kent in Moscow; murder of Mary C. Hastings by Robert C. Kent; Franklin Delano Roosevelt.
  - Folder 130. Elizabeth A. P. Kent Darling to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1894-1941, 12 items. (Series-folder 1:130)
  - Folder 131. Correspondence - Elizabeth A. P. Kent Darling to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers Undated, 10 items. (Series-folder 1:131)
  - Folder 132. Correspondence - Elizabeth A. P. Kent Darling to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers Undated, 13 items. (Series-folder 1:132)
  - Folder 133. Correspondence - Elizabeth A. P. Kent Darling to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers Undated, 15 items. (Series-folder 1:133)
  - Folder 134. Correspondence - Elizabeth A. P. Kent Darling to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers Undated, 15 items. (Series-folder 1:134)
  - Folder 135. Correspondence - Elizabeth A. P. Kent Darling to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers Undated, 15 items. (Series-folder 1:135)
  - Folder 136. Correspondence - Elizabeth A. P. Darling Withers to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers Undated, 15 items. (Series-folder 1:136)
  - Folder 138. Correspondence - Elizabeth A. P. Kent Darling to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers Undated, 15 items. (Series-folder 1:137)
  - Folder 139. Correspondence - Elizabeth A. P. Kent Darling to Anastasia Pleasants Smith Kent Undated, 10 items. (Series-folder 1:139)
  - Folder 140. Correspondence - Elizabeth A. P. Darling - Various Correspondents 1909-1910, Undated, 5 items. (Series-folder 1:140)
    Correspondents include: Mrs. J. K. Alter, Robert Edwin Withers Sr., and Flora McIvor Stuart.
  - Folder 141. Correspondence - Elizabeth A. P. Kent Darling - Incoming 1883-1942, Undated, 13 items. (Series-folder 1:141)
    Correspondents include: Elizabeth Needham re: bombing of London in World War II; William Patton Kent, Mrs. W. H. Fioller, Flora McIvor Stuart, Nelle Powell Payne Darling, Charlotte Miller Kent, Katharine DeFrees, and Elizabeth S. McAlpine.
  - Folder 142. Correspondence - Joseph Cloyd Kent to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1929-1932, 12 items. (Series-folder 1:142)
  - Folder 143. Correspondence - Joseph Cloyd Kent to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1933-1939, 9 items. (Series-folder 1:143)
  - Folder 144. Correspondence - Joseph Cloyd Kent to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1941-1951, Undated, 7 items. (Series-folder 1:144)
  - Folder 145. Correspondence - Ellen Douglas Stuart to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1932-1941, 10 items. (Series-folder 1:145)
  - Folder 146. Correspondence - Ellen Douglas Stuart to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers 1942-1947, 14 items. (Series-folder 1:146)
  - Folder 147. Correspondence - Ellen Douglas Stuart to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers Undated, 15 items. (Series-folder 1:147)
  - Folder 149. Correspondence - Ellen Douglas Stuart to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers Undated, 15 items. (Series-folder 1:148)
  - Folder 149. Correspondence - Ellen Douglas Stuart to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers Undated, 18 items. (Series-folder 1:149)
  - Folder 150. Correspondence - Janet Ann Carter Ambler 1880-1889, 8 items. (Series-folder 1:150)
    Correspondents include: E. Lewis Carter, F. G. Cross, Tyler Claiborne, and Harry Stinson.
  - Folder 151. Correspondence - Janet Ann Carter 1890-1898, Undated, 5 items. (Series-folder 1:151)
    Correspondents include: E. Mair, Elizabeth Royal Withers Carter, and Willie Clare Withers.
  - Folder 152. Janet Ann Withers Cook Boyd 1890-1898, Undated, 5 items. (Series-folder 1:152)
    Correspondents include: Henry Cook and Waller Massie Boyd.
  - Folder 153. Correspondence - Miscellaneous 1879-1838, 11 items. (Series-folder 1:153)
    Correspondents include: Mary Virginia Royall Withers, E. P. Goggin, Peirce Sanders, Elizabeth Royall Withers Carter, and William Page Dame.
  - Folder 154. Correspondence - Miscellaneous Undated, 9 items. (Series-folder 1:154)
    Correspondents include: Charlotte Kent Pinckney, Katherine Taylor Reed, and Josephine Withers Read.
  - Folder 155. Correspondence - Putney - Watts Family 1855-1956, Undated, 11 items. (Series-folder 1:155)
    Correspondents include: S. Putney Brown and Eliza Putney Watts.
  - Folder 156. Correspondence - Wedding Invitations 1894-1954, 14 items. (Series-folder 1:156)
    Wedding invitations for: Josephine Lillian Belden and Walter Beatty Jackson; Elizabeth Belden Kent and Edward Crosby Darling; Agnes Palmer Lewis and Harry Clinton Ford; Annie Hendren Patrick and William Patrick Kent; Dorothy Mosher O'Hara and Dion Keith Kerr; Eileen Allen and Charles Peirce Macgill; Frances Glover and Robert Edwin Withers Jr.; Elizabeth Lawson and Henry Andrew Jaeger; Portia Tatem and Benjamin Harold Hosler; Mary Terry and Charles O'Ferrall Thompson; Phoebe Kent and Herman Frederic Scholl; Nancy Jane Poage and Alfred Harris Evans; Anne Davidson Williams and Myles Russell Hutchinson; and Mary Dorothea Allen and Douglas West Poage Jr.
  - Folder 157. Correspondence - Wedding Invitations Undated, 11 items. (Series-folder 1:157)
    Wedding invitations for: Clarissa Halstead Stem and E. Fontaine Broun; Catharine Hardin and Robert Wilbur Curry; Marguerite Saunders and Eugene Davis; Harriet La Salle Dorrance and David Marshall Humphrey; Charlotte Johnston Miller and Joseph Cloyd Kent; Mary Spencer Gordon and John Frederick Kraft Jr.; Virginia Peyton Broun and Robert William Lawson Jr.; Frani Blough and Curt Muser; Ruth Tunstall Graham and Robert Lee Payne Jr.; Margaret Elizabeth Fleming and Kenneth Olney Rhodes; and Frances Randolph Howard and Robert Gilchrist Robb.
  - Folder 158. Correspondence - Invitations - Miscellaneous 1929-1937, 7 items. (Series-folder 1:158)
- Series II. Withers Genealogy Book Correspondence and Records 1939-1946, 30 folders.
- Series III. Genealogical Records 1892-1950, Undated, 9 folders.
- Series IV. Examiner of Records to the Auditor of Public Accounts - Correspondence and Reports 1896 - 1907, Undated, 50 folders.
- Series V. Religious Records 1894 - 1944, Undated, 4 folders.
- Series VI. Legal Records 1883-1938, Undated, 4 folders.
- Series VII. Financial Records 1896 - 1953, Undated, 54 folders.
- Series VIII. Photographs 1912 - 1943, Undated, 3 folders.
- Series IX. Miscellaneous Records 1933 - 1945, Undated, 5 folders.